

MIHAILO MAKSA

SENIOR SMART CONTRACT ENGINEER

🖸 Novi Sad, Serbia | 🕻 +381 63202961 | 🔀 <u>mihajlomaksa9@gmail.com</u>

in LinkedIn | Github | #

mihailomaksa.com

ABOUT ME

As a seasoned and highly skilled senior smart contract engineer with 4+ years of experience in the smart contract development, I bring a deep expertise and passion for the crypto, DeFi, and web3 space to every project. My specialty is in the solidity smart contract development for a wide range of use cases.

I have a thorough understanding of DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, dApps, web3, crypto, and blockchain in general, and I've been working on various web3 projects since 2018.

Also, I speak English with a native-level fluency, and have a proven ability to communicate effectively and collaborate remotely, which makes me a valuable asset for any team.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Economics, Major in Business Informatics

University of Novi Sad, Faculty of Economics October 2019 - Present

PRIOR EXPERIENCE

ScaleRoad LLC / Full Stack Web Developer

Investment research management SaaS platform July 2018 - March 2019

Avix Finance / Smart Contract Engineer

Tokenized volatility protocol designed to track the price of VIX on-chain March 2019 - December 2020

LongTerm Finance / Smart Contract Engineer

Tokenized index fund protocol tracking the market cap of the entire altcoin market December 2020 - June 2022

MAJR, Inc. / Senior Smart Contract Engineer

Web3 media company focused on the video content curation & digital assets June 2022 - Present

Smart Contract Security Audits

My code has been audited by the professional smart contract security auditors (e.g. Hacken) with close to perfect scores. See audit 1 and audit 2 for more details.

MY SKILLS













Solidity

Hardhat

IPFS

Ethers.is

React

TypeScript